Finding Aid for Law School (University of Michigan), 1852-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Faculty Files, 1859-1960
  - Personnel Files
    - Bishop, William W., Jr. (includes photo), 1952-1988 (Box 119)
      [PR RESTRICTED until January 1, 2018 ]
    - Blair, Patricia N., 1969 (Box 112)
    - Blume, William Wirt, 1945-1982 (Box 112)
    - Body, Judith, 1964 (Box 112)
    - Bolgar, Vera, 1951-1976 (Box 119)
    - Bonassies, Janine, 1952 (Box 112)
    - Bonfield, Arthur E., 1970 (Box 112)
    - Borgsdorf, Charles (includes photo), 1973 (Box 119)
    - Bourgeois, Jacques H.J. (Win 1976), 1975 (Box 119)
    - Boyce, George K., 1957 (Box 112)
    - Boyd, Willard L., 1962-1964 (Box 112)
    - Brainerd, Julia C., 1951 (Box 112)
    - Braucher, Robert, 1962 (Box 112)
    - Bray, Dorothy D., 1947 (Box 112)
    - Breakey, James, 1964-1969 (Box 112)
    - Brill, Ralph L., 1960 (Box 112)
    - Brilmayer, Lea (Sum 1982--Conflicts) (Box 119)
    - Brodley, Joseph F. (Fall 1982) (Box 119)
    - Broeder, Dale W., 1963 (Box 112)
    - Browder, Olin L., Jr. (c.v.), 1965 (Box 112)
    - Brown, Elizabeth H.G., 1954-1999; 2 folders (Box 119)
      [PR RESTRICTED until January 1, 2029 ]
    - Buergenthal, Thomas, 1967 (Box 112)
    - Bunker, Robert Emmet, 1955 (Box 112)
    - Burnham, William, 1977-1984 (Box 119)
    - Burt, Robert A., 1967-1989 (Box 119)
      [PR RESTRICTED until January 1, 2019 ]
    - Buxbaum, Richard M., 1965 (Box 112)
    - Calkins, Stephen (Sum 1985) (Box 119)
    - Campbell, Angus, 1968-1980 (Box 119)
    - Carrington, Paul D., 1964-1977 (Box 119)
    - Carter, Robert L. (Fall 1976) (Box 119)
    - Chasson, Gloria Thelma, 1952 (Box 112)
    - Choate, Robert, 1960-1998 (Box 119)
    - Christensen, Craig, 1970-1971 (Box 112)
    - Christensen, Thomas G.S. (Win 1977), 1976 (Box 119)
    - Christie, George C. (Sum 1970 and Sum 1977), 1970-1977 (Box 119)
    - Coffee, John C. (Sum 1979), 1978-1979 (Box 119)
    - Coffey, Hobart, 1945-1969 (Box 112)
    - Coffey, Ronald J. (Fall 1974) (Box 119)
    - Cohen, Donald S., 1976-1978 (Box 119)
    - Cohn, Stuart R. (Win 1983), 1982 (Box 119)
    - Conard, Alfred F., 1966 (Box 112)
    - Cooper, Frank E., 1948-1968 (Box 112)
    - Cooperrider, Luke K. (c.v.), 1965 (Box 112)
    - Corty, Susanne Pisko, 1948 (Box 112)
    - Couch, Harvey C. (Sum 1966 and Sum 1970), 1966-1970 (Box 112)
    - Covington, Robert (Sum 1971) (Box 112)
    - Cramton, Roger C., 1961-1984 (Box 120)
    - Cribbet, John E., 1963 (Box 112)
    - Croft, Barbara B. (Sum 1973) (Box 120)
    - Cross, Harry M. (Fall 1972) (Box 120)
    - Cunningham, Roger A., 1963-1994 (Box 120)
      [PR RESTRICTED until January 1, 2024 ]
    - Currie, David, 1964-1967 (Box 112)
    - Dainow, Joseph, 1957 (Box 112)
    - Dando, Shegemitsu, 1958-1984 (Box 120)
    - Daniel, Roy J. (1980/81 and Sum1981--Clinic), 1979-1980 (Box 120)
    - Dauer, Edward A. (Sum 1972), 1971-1972 (Box 119)
    - Davis, Wylie H., 1958 (Box 112)
    - Dawson, George L., 1969-1970 (Box 112)
    - Dawson, John P., 1944-1993 (Box 120)
    - Day, Richard E., 1962 (Box 112)
    - Degnan, Ronan E., 1962; 1969 (Box 112)
    - Dellinger, Walter E. III (Sum 1977), 1976-1977 (Box 120)
    - De Pauw, Frans (Win 1973), 1972 (Box 120)
    - Derrett, John D.M., 1970 (Box 112)
    - Desmedt, Herwig (includes photo), 1962-1964 (Box 112)
    - Deutsch, Jan G. (Sum 1975), 1974 (Box 120)
    - DeVine, Edmond F., 1951-1979 (Box 120)
    - Dickinson, Edwin D. (Member of the faculty, 1919-1933), 1966 (Box 112)
    - Dickinson, Martin B., Jr. (Fall 1970), 1970-1971 (Box 112)
    - Dimond, Paul R., 1977-1985 (Box 120)
    - Dixon, Bonnie, 1989 (Box 120)
    - Dodyk, Paul M. (Sum 1965), 1964-1965 (Box 112)
    - Doehring, Karl, 1966-1970 (Box 112)
    - Dolan, John F. (Win 1984), 1983 (Box 120)
    - Dolzer, Rudolf (Fall 1984 and Fall 1985), 1984-1986 (Box 120)
    - Donahue, Charles, 1971-1979 (Box 120)
    - Dooley, Michael P. (Sum 1974) (Box 120)
    - Drake, Joseph H., 1947 (Box 112)
      (Member of the faculty, 1907-1930 includes photo)
    - Drinan, Robert F. (Sum 1984), 1983-1984 (Box 120)
    - Drobnig, Ulrich, 1956; 1964 (Box 112)
    - Duke, Steven, 1967-1968 (Box 112)
    - Dunning, Harrison C. (Fall 1973) (Box 120)
    - Durfee, Edgar N., 1941-1958 (Box 112)
    - Eckhardt, Willard L., 1962 (Box 112)
    - Edwards, Harry, 1969-1992 (Box 112)
      [PR RESTRICTED until January 1, 2022 ]
    - Effland, Richard W. (Sum 1970) (Box 112)
    - Effland, Richard (Sum 1974) (Box 120)
    - Eglit, Howard C., 1967 (Box 112)
    - Elkins, Bettye (Win 1978), 1977 (Box 120)
    - Elkouri, Frank, 1961 (Box 112)
    - Elliott, Shelden D., 1957 (Box 112)
    - Engdahl, David E., 1971 (Box 112)
    - Engel, David M. (Sum 1984), 1983-1984 (Box 120)
    - Enker, Arnold N. (Sum 1973 and Sum 1977), 1972-1979 (Box 120)
    - Epstein, David G. (Win 1972 and Sum 1976), 1971 (Box 120)
    - Estep, Samuel D., 1965Faber, Tom (Sum 1969) (Box 112)
    - Farnsworth, E. Allan, 1958 (Box 112)
    - Fawcett, Kim R. (Adjunct Lecturer, 1980--Criminal Appellate Practice Course), 1979 (Box 120)
    - Feingold, Eugene N., 1965-1966 (Box 112)
    - Feinsinger, Nathan P., 1957 (Box 112)
    - Feldman, Joseph D., 1967 (Box 112)
    - Fellows, Mary Louise (1978/79) (Box 120)
    - Ferguson, Larry J. (1981--Tax Clinic) (Box 120)
    - Fikentscher, Wolfgang, 1966-1976 (Box 120)
    - Filippov, Sviatoslav (Senior Researcher--Fall 1976), 1975-1976 (Box 120)
    - Findley, Roger William (Win 1982--Property), 1981-1983 (Box 120)
    - Finkin, Matthew W. (1980/81--Labor Law and Administrative Law) (Box 120)
    - Flanagan, Terence Roberts (Lecturer, 1976/77--Criminal Appellate Practice) (Box 120)
    - Fleming, John G. (Sum 1967 and Sum 1974), 1967-1973 (Box 120)
    - Flynn, John J., 1966 (Box 112)
    - Folk, Ernest L., 1965-1966 (Box 112)
    - Ford, Harold A.J., 1963-1965 (Box 112)
    - Frankel, Tamar, 1983-1984 (Box 120)
    - Fraser, George, 1963-1965 (Box 112)
    - Freedman, James O. (Sum 1971) (Box 112)
    - Freeman, Alwyn V., 1962 (Box 112)
    - Fried, Jules (Instructor, 1971/72) (Box 112)
    - Friedenthal, Jack H. (Sum 1971) (Box 112)
    - Friedman, Jane M. (Win 1971 and Win 1983), 1970; 1982-1983 (Box 120)
    - Frowein, Jochen Abraham (Sum 1978), 1977-1978 (Box 120)
    - Furnish, Dale B., 1969 (Box 112)
    - Furrow, Barry R. (1981/82) (Box 120)
    - Galvin, Charles O'Neill, 1957 (Box 112)
    - Gamble, E. James (Adjunct Lecturer, Win 1980), 1979-1981 (Box 120)
    - Gardner, Consuelo Regina, 1949 (Box 112)
    - Gass, Edward W., 1966 (Box 112)
    - Gaus, William A. (Instructor, 1971/72) (Box 112)
    - Geck, Wilhelm Karl, 1960-1965, Gellhorn, Ernest A. (Sum 1975), 1974 (Box 120)
    - George, B. James, Jr., 1952-1978 (Box 120)
    - Gesmer, Ellen (Assistant Professor, Fall 1983--Clinic) (Box 120)
    - Gifford, Daniel J. (Fall 1984) (Box 120)
    - Gilbert, Larry, 1978 (Box 120)
    - Gillette, Clayton P. (Fall 1983) (Box 120)
    - Gilson, Ronald J. (Lecturer, Fall 1977), 1976-1978 (Box 120)
    - Gobert, James Joseph (1970/71 and Sum 1978) (Box 120)
    - Goldberg, Stephen B. (Sum 1971) (Box 112)
    - Goldman, Edward B., 1973-1978 (Box 120)
    - Goldman, Marc L., 1979 (Box 120)
    - Gomes, Mary B., 1961-1977 (Box 120)
    - Goodrich, Leon R., 1963 (Box 112)
    - Goodman, Richard M., 1975 (Box 120)
    - Goodwin, Bert Z. (Sum 1979--Administrative Law), 1978-1979 (Box 120)
    - Gordon, Wendy J. (1984/85) (Box 120)
    - Gorla, Luigi, 1957-1958 (Box 112)
    - Gorman, Robert A., 1968 (Box 112)
    - Gorske, Robert Herman, 1958 (Box 112)
    - Goss, James W., 1977-1982 (Box 120)
    - Graham, Kenneth W., Jr., 1967-1968 (Box 112)
    - Gray, Whitmore (c.v.), circa 1965 (Box 112)
    - Gressman, Eugene (Sum 1969), 1968-1969 (Box 112)
    - Gribble, James J., 1966-1971 (Box 112)
    - Grismore, Grover G., 1942-1951 (Box 112)
    - Grossfeld, Bernhard T. (Win 1969 and Win 1971), 1968-1971 (Box 112)
    - Grzybowski, Kazimierz, 1960-1962 (Box 113)
    - Gunn, Alan (Win 1983), 1982 (Box 120)
    - Hadari, Yitzhak, 1975 (Box 120)
    - Hagman, Donald G. (Sum 1980) (Box 120)
    - Hamson, Charles J. (includes photo), 1956-1960 (Box 113)
    - Hanslowe, Kurt L. (Win 1982--Labor Law and Arbitration), 1981 (Box 120)
    - Harris, Lawrence Kenneth, 1959 (Box 113)
    - Harris, Robert James, circa 1965 (Box 113)
    - Hartley, Trevor C. (Win 1985), 1984 (Box 120)
    - Hartman, Susan D. (Adjunct Lecturer, Win 1980) (Box 113)
    - Harvey, William B., 1951-1966; 1999 (Box 113)
    - Havighurst, Clark C. (Fall 1983) (Box 120)
    - Hawkins, Carl S., 1957-1972 (Box 120)
    - Haworth, Charles R. (Sum 1975) (Box 120)
    - Hazard, Geoffrey C., 1962 (Box 113)
    - Headrick, William C., 1963-1964 (Box 113)
    - Heenen, Jacques, 1964 (Box 113)
    - Helfer, Ray E., 1977 (Box 120)
    - Henderson, Roger C. (Win 1976), 1975 (Box 120)
    - Herman, Lawrence, 1968 (Box 113)
    - Herrmann, Joachim (Fall 1983), 1982-1985 (Box 120)
    - Higginbotham, A. Leon, Jr., 1973-1975 (Box 120)
    - Hirano, Ryuichi, 1967 (Box 113)
    - Hirsch, Ronald L., 1970 (Box 113)
    - Hjorth, Roland L. (Fall 1980) (Box 120)
    - Hoffman, Peter, 1972-1973 (Box 120)
    - Hollinger, Joan (1981/82) (Box 120)
    - Hovenkamp, Herbert (Win 1986), 1984-1985 (Box 120)
    - Hyde, Alan S. (1983/84) (Box 120)
    - Hyde, James Nevins (Win 1971), 1970 (Box 113)
    - Hydeman, Lee M., 1958 (Box 113)
    - Israel, Stuart M., 1973-1974 (Box 120)
    - Jack, Howard A. (1970/71) (Box 113)
    - Jacobson, Peter (Instructor, 1971/72) (Box 113)
    - James, Laylin K., 1949-1967 (Box 113)
    - Jennings, Richard W., 1963 (Box 113)
    - Johnsen, Theodore, 1968 (Box 113)
    - Jones, Gareth (Sum 1983) (Box 120)
    - Jones, Robert A. (Development Director), 1973 (Box 120)
    - Jones, Thomas L., 1961-1964 (Box 113)
    - Jordan, Ellen R. (Sum 1979--Unfair Trade Practices), 1978-1979 (Box 120)
    - Josephson, Michael, 1967 (Box 113)
    - Joswick, David Daniel, 1969 (Box 113)
    - Judge, Judith W. (Adjunct Instructor), 1975 (Box 120)
    - Julin, Joseph R., 1959-1993 (Box 120)
    - Kadish, Sanford H., 1961-1964 (Box 113)
    - Kalo, Joseph J., 1971-1974 (Box 120)
    - Kane, Mary Kay (Win 1981), 1980 (Box 120)
    - Kanowitz, Leo (Sum 1974), 1973 (Box 120)
    - Karlstrom, Sten Olaf, 1965 (Box 113)
    - Katz, Lewis R., 1965 (Box 113)
    - Katz, Sanford, 1967 (Box 113)
    - Kauper, Paul G., 1956-1977 (Box 120)
    - Kaye, Orin W., Jr., 1965 (Box 113)
    - Keller, W. Richard, 1966 (Box 113)
    - Kent, Charles A., 1945 (Box 113)
      (Member of the faculty 1883-1884 photo and negative)
    - Kerr, William T. (Adjunct Assistant Professor), 1975 (Box 120)
    - Kester, John, 1968-1969 (Box 113)
    - Kimball, Spencer L., 1955-1971 (Box 113)
    - Kinami, Atsushi (Win 1983), 1982-1983 (Box 120)
    - King, Patricia A. (Sum 1976) (Box 120)
    - Kirgis, Frederic L., Jr. (Win 1983), 1982 (Box 120)
    - Kirkpatrick, Laird, 1968 (Box 113)
    - Kirtley, Edward Alan, 1978 (Box 120)
    - Kitch, Edmund W. (Sum 1971) (Box 113)
    - Klare, Karl E. (Sum 1981--Labor Law), 1980-1981 (Box 120)
    - Knauss, Robert L., 1957-1970 (Box 113)
    - Kolb, Gary Jack (Adjunct Assistant Professor, Win 1977) (Box 120)
    - Kornfield, Susan Margaret, 1997 (Box 120)
    - Krause, Harry D. (Win 1981--Family Law and Welfare Law), 1980 (Box 120)
    - Krogsrud, James, 1983 (Box 120)
    - Krueger, Robert, 1970 (Box 113)
    - Kuklin, Bailey H., 1970-1974 (Box 120)
    - Kuwabara, Masahiro (Research Scholar, Fall 1975), 1974-1975 (Box 120)
    - Lachman, Judith A. (1984/85) (Box 120)
    - Lachmann, Per (Win 1982--External Relations of the EEC), 1981-1982 (Box 120)
    - Ladd, Charles J. (1976/77), 1976-1977 (Box 120)
    - LaFave, Wayne R., 1964 (Box 113)
    - Lancaster, Arthalu L. (Clinical Law), 1976 (Box 120)
    - Langbein, John H. (Sum 1975), 1975-1976 (Box 120)
    - Lange, David L. (Sum 1978) (Box 120)
    - Langer, Margaret, 1964 (Box 113)
    - LaRene, N.C. DeDay, 1968 (Box 113)
    - Laughlin, Stanley K., 1962 (Box 113)
    - Lauwaars, R.H. (1979/80), 1978-1991 (Box 120)
      [PR RESTRICTED until January 1, 2021 ]
    - Lawson, Frederick H., 1958-1959 (Box 113)
    - Leavell, Robert N., 1965 (Box 113)
    - Lee, Melissa N. (Win 1979--Clinic) (Box 120)
    - Leidy, Paul A., 1948-1970; 1993 (Box 113)
    - Leslie, Douglas L. (Fall 1976) (Box 120)
    - Lesnick, Howard (Sum 1977) (Box 120)
    - Levine, Barbara Ruth, 1977-1979 (Box 120)
    - Levit, Jay L., 1964-1965 (Box 113)
    - Li, Victor, 1966-1968 (Box 113)
    - Liberman, Robert, 1962-1963 (Box 113)
    - Light, John R., 1967 (Box 113)
    - Logan, James K. (Sum 1976), 1976-1977 (Box 120)
    - Lowe, James B., 1961 (Box 113)
    - Lowndes, Charles L.B., 1963 (Box 113)
    - Lugar, Marlyn E., 1965 (Box 113)
    - Luther, Pamela G. (Fall 1977) (Box 120)
    - Magid, Martin K. (Clinical Instructor--Elderly), 1975 (Box 120)
    - Malone, Wex S., 1963 (Box 113)
    - Mancke, Richard B., 1971-1974 (Box 120)
    - Manne, Henry G., 1963-1964 (Box 113)
    - Marsh, Norman K., 1963-1964 (Box 113)
    - Marshall, Donald G. (Sum 1980--Torts) (Box 120)
    - Martin, James A., 1970-1986 (Box 120)
    - Martin, John H. (Win 1977), 1976-1977 (Box 120)
    - Martindale, Roger (includes photo), 1974-1976 (Box 120)
    - Mason, John, 1972-1978 (Box 120)
    - Massel, Mark, 1963-1964 (Box 113)
    - Mathijsen, Pierre, 1961 (Box 113)
    - McCauley, Matthew P.T., 1968-1973 (Box 120)
    - McCracken, David E., 1966 (Box 113)
    - Means, Robert C. (Sum 1973) (Box 120)
    - Meisenholder, Robert, 1958 (Box 113)
    - Merrifield, Leroy S., 1959-1961; 1967 (Box 113)
    - Merrill, Maurice H., 1960 (Box 113)
    - Messing, Ellen J. (Adjunct Instructor, Win 1982--Clinic) (Box 120)
    - Mestmacker, Ernest, 1963-1975 (Box 121)
    - Meyers, Charles, 1963 (Box 113)
    - Michel, Jacques (Win 1977), 1975-1976 (Box 121)
    - Miller, Arthur R., 1964-1972 (Box 121)
    - Miller, William T. (1984.85), 1983-1985 (Box 121)
    - Million, Elmer, 1964 (Box 113)
    - Mills, Stephen J. (Instructor, 1972/73) (Box 113)
    - Mishkin, Paul J., 1961 (Box 113)
    - Mittenthal, Richard (Adjunct Lecturer, Win 1983), 1982 (Box 121)
    - Moran, Michael C., 1972-1979 (Box 121)
    - Morgan, Wilda B., 1963-1964 (Box 113)
    - Muller-Freienfels, Wolfram, 1962-1963 (Box 113)
    - Nagel, Robert F. (Sum 1984) (Box 121)
    - Needham, Roger A., 1958-1962 (Box 113)
    - Nelson, Grant S., 1965-1971 (Box 113)
    - Newman, George G., 1966 (Box 113)
    - Nicholson, Thomas Laurence, 1959 (Box 113)
    - Niebler, Horst, 1965-1984 (Box 121)
    - Nordby, Virginia, 1972-1978 (Box 121)
    - Norville, Craig H., 1969 (Box 113)
    - Nussbaum, Michael, 1963-1964 (Box 113)
    - Nygh, Peter E. (Win 1977), 1976 (Box 121)
    - Oaks, Dallin H., 1967-1968 (Box 113)
    - O'Connell, Jeffrey, 1965-1975 (Box 121)
    - Olavarria, Julio A., 1967-1968 (Box 113)
    - O'Neal, F. Hodge, 1964-1965 (Box 113)
    - Oppenheim, S. Chesterfield, 1947-1974; 1988 (Box 121)
    - Orlov, Alexander, 1962-1964 (Box 113)
    - Osakwe, Christopher (Win 1981--International Organizations), 1980 (Box 121)
    - Painter, William H., 1964-1965 (Box 113)
    - Palmer, George E., 1944-1978; 1994 (Box 121)
    - Palmer, L. Guy, 1979; 1991 (Box 121)
    - Palmer, Robert C., 1978-1982 (Box 121)
    - Parella, Robert E., 1960 (Box 113)
    - Park, Roger C. (Fall 1984) (Box 121)
    - Paulus, Camille, 1974 (Box 121)
    - Payson, Martin D., 1963 (Box 113)
    - Pearce, Jack Richard, 1955-1985 (Box 121)
    - Peck, Cornelius J. (1973/74), 1973-1974 (Box 121)
    - Pedrick, Willard Hyram, 1961 (Box 113)
    - Peng, Ming-Min (Win 1972), 1971 (Box 113)
    - Pepe, Steven D., 1973-1997 (Box 121)
    - Peschel, John L. (Win 1976), 1975 (Box 121)
    - Phillips, David M., 1985 (Box 121)
    - Plant, Marcus L., 1959-1984 (Box 121)
    - Plater, Zygmunt J.B. (Win 1980), 1979 (Box 121)
    - Polasky, Alan N. (includes photo), 1957-1978 (Box 121)
    - Pollak, Louis H., 1961 (Box 113)
    - Polsby, Daniel D. (Sum 1982--Torts), 1982-1983 (Box 121)
    - Pooley, Beverley John (c.v.), 1996 (Box 113)
    - Poulton, William D.C., 1961-1962 (Box 113)
    - Powell, Richard R., 1958-1959 (Box 113)
    - Powell, Sinclair, 1966 (Box 113)
    - Powers, Williams C., Jr. (Sum 1981--Torts) (Box 121)
    - Price, John R. (Win 1982--Trusts and Estates I and Estate Planning), 1981 (Box 121)
    - Rabban, David M., 1985-1986 (Box 121)
    - Rehbinder, Eckard (Fall 1980), 1979-1980 (Box 121)
    - Reimann, Mathias (Win 1985), 1983-1985 (Box 121)
    - Reingold, Paul D. (Adjunct Lecturer, Win 1981--Clinic) (Box 121)
    - Reiss, Albert J., Jr., 1969 (Box 113)
    - Reitze, Arnold W., Jr., 1964-1965 (Box 113)
    - Reppy, William Jr. (Sum 1973) (Box 121)
    - Rice, James E., 1968 (Box 113)
    - Rice, Ralph S. (Fall 1975) (Box 121)
    - Riesenfeld, Stefan A. (Fall 1972), 1971-1973 (Box 121)
    - Rivera, Rhonda R., 1974-1976 (Box 121)
    - Robinson, Cyril D., 1965 (Box 113)
    - Rodriguez-Restrepo, Sergio, 1969 (Box 113)
    - Roemele, Eugene, 1957-1968 (Box 113)
    - Rohr, Richard D., 1976; 1979 (Box 121)
    - Rosberg, Gerald M., 1974-1991 (Box 121)
    - Rosenblum, Victor G. (Sum 1979--Torts) (Box 121)
    - Rothschild, Donald P. (Win 1976), 1975 (Box 121)
    - Rothstein, Paul F., 1963-1967 (Box 113)
    - Ruland, Virginia L., 1956-1958; 1981 (Box 121)
    - Rupp, Hans, 1962-1963; 1970 (Box 113)
    - Russell, Alice J., 1958-1963 (Box 113)
    - Sachs, Theodore (Win 1976), 1975-1976 (Box 121)
    - Sager, Lawrence G. (Sum 1978) (Box 121)
    - St. Antoine, Theodore J. (c.v.), circa 1995 (Box 113)
    - Saltzburg, Stephen A. (Sum 1975), 1974 (Box 121)
    - Schachter, Oscar, 1962 (Box 113)
    - Schattefroh, Reiner, 1962 (Box 113)
    - Schermers, Henricus G., 1968 (Box 113)
    - Schindler, Dietrich, 1961 (Box 113)
    - Schulman, Stephen H. (Win 1972), 1971 (Box 113)
    - Schulte, Henry J., 1974 (Box 121)
    - Schwartz, Elizabeth R. (1976) (Box 121)
    - Schwartz, Gary (Sum 1972), 1971-1972 (Box 121)
    - Schwartz, Herman, 1967-1968 (Box 113)
    - Schwartz, Murray L., 1963-1964 (Box 113)
    - Scoles, Eugene F. (Sum 1978) (Box 121)
    - Sebert, John A. (Sum 1973) (Box 113)
    - Seikaly, Daniel S., 1971-1974 (Box 121)
    - Sell, William E., 1957 (Box 113)
    - Sepulveda, Cesar, 1966-1967 (Box 113)
    - Seymour, Robert Vincent, 1970 (Box 113)
    - Shafii, Mohammad, 1971-1972 (Box 121)
    - Shanker, Morris G., 1963-1964 (Box 113)
    - Shapiro, E. Donald, 1960-1967 (Box 113)
    - Shapo, Marshall (Sum 1973) (Box 113)
    - Shartel, Burke, 1939-1959; 1996 (Box 113)
    - Shervington, Walter W., 1969 (Box 113)
    - Shiffrin, Steven H. (Fall 1984) (Box 121)
    - Shillingford, George, 1961-1962 (Box 113)
    - Shipman, Morgan (Fall 1973) (Box 121)
    - Shimm, Melvin G. (Win 1973), 1972 (Box 121)
    - Shulman, Stephen N., 1959 (Box 113)
    - Siegel, Stanley, 1966-1972 (Box 121)
    - Silberman, Linda (Sum 1972), 1972-1973 (Box 121)
    - Simes, Lewis M., 1939-1975 (Box 113)
    - Simon, Barry S. (Lecturer, Fall 1979--Seminar-White Collar Crimes) (Box 121)
    - Smith, Allan F., 1974-1994 (Box 121)
    - Smith, Arthur M., 1954-1968 (Box 113)
    - Smith, George P. III, 1965-1966 (Box 113)
    - Snowden, John (Instructor, 1971/72) (Box 113)
    - Snyder, Ann E. (Research Associate--Clinical Law), 1976-1977 (Box 121)
    - Sobeloff, Jonathon (Sum 1978) (Box 121)
    - Sobol, Richard B., 1968-1969 (Box 113)
    - Spiegel, Mark, 1968 (Box 113)
    - Spitz, Stephen L. (Instructor, 1972/73), 1972-1973 (Box 121)
    - Stason, E. Blythe, 1958-1972 (Box 113)
    - Steadman, John M. (Sum 1976) (Box 121)
      [PR RESTRICTED until January 1, 2069 ]
    - Stein, Ted L. (Fall 1983), 1983-1985 (Box 121)
    - Steingold, Fred S., 1961-1965 (Box 113)
    - Steinheimer, Roy L., Jr., 1950-1968 (Box 113)
    - Stewart, George C., 1971 (Box 113)
    - Stoll, Hans, 1963 (Box 113)
    - Stone, Bradford (Fall 1971), 1971-1972 (Box 113)
    - Stone, Christopher D. (Sum 1972) (Box 113)
    - Stone, Christopher D. (Sum 1985) (Box 121)
    - Strong, John W., 1965 (Box 113)
    - Sturgis, William S., 1963-1964 (Box 113)
    - Sugeno, Kazuo (1975/76), 1974-1976 (Box 121)
    - Summers, Robert S. (Sum 1974), 1972-1974 (Box 114)
    - Sunderland, Edson R., 1939-1964 (Box 114)
    - Taniguchi, Yasuhei, 1976 (Box 121)
    - Tarlock, Dan A. (Win 1982), 1981 (Box 121)
    - Tatel, David S., 1966-1970 (Box 114)
    - Thorpe, Philip C., 1964-1965 (Box 114)
    - Tooley, Janet M. (1979--Criminal Appellate Practice Course), 1978-1979 (Box 121)
    - Tracy, John E., 1939-1959 (Box 114)
    - Trautman, Herman L., 1963-1964 (Box 114)
    - Trigg, Paul R., Jr. (Win 1973), 1972 (Box 121)
    - Tulecke, Hazel B., 1948-1949 (Box 114)
    - Turner, John N., 1963-1965 (Box 114)
    - Twerski, Aaron D. (Fall 1984) (Box 121)
    - Ulmer, Eugen Richard, 1957 (Box 114)
    - Van Hoek, Peter J., 1984 (Box 121)
    - Vercruysse, Robert M. (Adjunct Lecturer, Win 1980), 1979 (Box 121)
    - Virtue, Maxine, 1948-1955 (Box 114)
    - Voegelin, Dorothy Dudgeonm, 1946-1948 (Box 114)
    - Waaben, Knud, 1961-1965 (Box 114)
    - Wade, John W. (Fall 1982) (Box 121)
    - Waite, John B., 1939-1967 (Box 114)
    - Wall, James D., 1961-1964 (Box 114)
    - Walsh, Denis, 1977 (Box 121)
    - Wang, Kenneth, 1961-1962 (Box 114)
    - Ward, Erica A. (Adjunct Lecturer, Win 1984), 1983 (Box 121)
    - Ward, Katherine E. (Writing and Advocacy), 1984 (Box 121)
    - Warden, Karl, 1964 (Box 114)
    - Wasserstrom, Richard, 1961-1963 (Box 114)
    - Waterson, Jane M., 1972 (Box 121)
    - Watson, Andrew S., 1958-1998 (Box 121)
    - Watson, W.A.J. (Fall 1977), 1977-1978 (Box 121)
    - Weintraub, Russell, 1964-1965 (Box 114)
    - Weisberger, June (Fall 1977) (Box 121)
    - Weistart, John C. (Sum 1980--Contracts), 1979-1980 (Box 121)
    - Wellman, Richard V., 1954-1984 (Box 121)
    - Weston, Glen E., 1963-1964 (Box 114)
    - Whitaker, Adelaide B., 1956 (Box 114)
    - White, James Boyd, 1982 (Box 121)
    - White, Michelle J., 1984-1988 (Box 121)
    - White, Patricia D. (1984/85) (Box 121)
    - White, Thomas R. III (Sum 1972) (Box 121)
    - Williams, Howard R. (Sum 1969) (Box 114)
    - Wilson, James G. (1978/79), 1978-1979 (Box 121)
    - Wolf, James Richard, 1959-1960 (Box 114)
    - Wolfman, Bernard (Sum 1982--Tax I) (Box 121)
    - Wotila, Roger (Jan 1, 1975-May 17, 1976) (Box 121)
    - Wright, Charles Alan, 1956 (Box 114)
    - Wright, L. Hart, 1947-1983 (Box 121)
    - Wright, Q., 1967 (Box 114)
    - Yntema, Hessel E. (includes photo), 1945-1969 (Box 114)
    - Yokota, Yozo (Win 1984), 1982-1983 (Box 121)
    - Yourd, Kenneth L., 1968-1969 (Box 114)
    - Zweigert, Konrad E. (includes photo), 1956-1957 (Box 114)
  - Publications, Research and Activities
    Publications, Research and Activities contains reports of research activities conducted by the faculty during the years 1963 through 1994.
    - Annual Report of Research in the University of Michigan Law School, 1963-1967; 5 folders (Box 115)
    - Faculty Report on Publications, 1982/83 and 1983/84, 1984 (Box 115)
    - Faculty Reports on Publications, Research and Activities, 1977/78-1993/94; 17 folders (Box 115)
    - Law School Faculty Publications, July 1977-June 1981; 1981 (Box 115)
  - Salaries
    The Salaries series contains lists of University of Michigan law professors' salaries, and those from other Big Ten universities, which were exchanged among the deans of the law schools.
    - Economic Status of Faculty, 1966-1987 (Box 115)
    - Faculty Salaries in University of Michigan and other Law Schools, 1965-1993 (Box 115)
- Student Activities and Organizations, 1894-1996; 4 linear feet